come here I love to fry you I
иди сюда Я люблю тебя прожаривать я
listen I
слушаю
always have a new topic today so this is the
у меня всегда сегодня новая тема так это
collapse of the Russian Federation Do you
распад Российской Федерации Как ты
think the peoples have the right to
считаешь народы имеют право на
self-determination
самоопределение
when Yakutia will hold a referendum on
когда Якутия проведет референдум о
independence will it be you will accept it
независимости это будет ты примешь это
and who will conduct it
а кто будет его проводить Расскажи
Kherson to hold a referendum And these are people in
Херсоне провести референ А это люди в
Yakutia who want to hold it so I’m
Якутии хотят провести так вот 14 года
looking at
смотрю
a referendum for 14 years there is a right to self-determination
референдум есть право на самоопределение
And you 14 have a right there are people
Причем ты 14 есть право есть люди
Wait wait We have Russia on a halt
Подожди подожди У нас Россия на Привал
to the Constitution and see the right to
на Конституцию причем смотри право на
resist does not depend on whether at all
сопротивление не зависит от того вообще
if we don’t have a Constitution  Russia is now being
если нету Конституцию нас России сейчас
asked, let’s consider what difference does it
спрашивают ещё рассмотрим какая разница
make, the right of peoples to
он есть же право народов на
self-determination, that is, when
самоопределение то есть когда
your Russia didn’t give a damn In the
наплевала ваша Россия наплевала В
ninety-third year on the Constitution, yes
девяносто третьем году на Конституцию да
In the ninety-third year, Yeltsin this
В девяносто третьем году Ельцин в этом
year America
году Америка
dissolved parliament, the parliament said that
распустил парламент парламент сказал что
Yeltsin had no authority Yes, and filed in  The
Ельцин не имел полномочий Да и подал в
Constitutional Court if it dissolved the
Конституционный суд если он распустил
constitutional court and shot the
конституционный суд и расстрелял из
parliament from tanks Since then, you have a military
танков парламент С тех пор у вас военная
junta,
хунта
everything is yes, therefore, the
всё да поэтому
federation was adopted in 94,
федерации была принята в 94 году
too Yeltsin Yeltsin Different
правильно тоже Ельцин Ельцин Разно
Yeltsin dispersed the parliament before shooting
Ельцин разогнал парламент до расстрелял
there,
там
look, that is, Yeltsin Yeltsin did
смотри то есть ель Ельцин Ельцин сделан
not make a constitutional coup, he  did not have the
не конституционный переворот он не имел
right to disperse the stream of the Constitution that
права разгонять поток Конституции что
was in 93 Yeltsin had the right to disperse the
было в 93 Ельцин имел право разогнать
parliament Listen, tell me the
парламент Слушай скажи
RSFSR was not there was a Constitution you
РСФСР было не было было Конституция вы
lived according to this Constitution, that is, 93 was
жили по этой Конституции то есть 93 было
your country Russia of the Russian Federation is
ваша страна Россия Российской Федерации
a brake, that is, 91 92 was not the Russian
тормоз то есть 91 92 не было Российской
Federation,
Федерации
I am hello most Russian  the Russian
я привет самый российский российское
Federation was the Constitution so the
именно Федерация Конституция так
Constitution was adopted modern until after the
Конституцию приняли современную до после
Yeltsin coup
ельцинского переворота
no
нет
93 December 12 until 123 in 92
93 год 12 декабря до 123 года в 92 году
that you didn’t have Russia was the Russian
что у вас не было Россия была Российская
Soviet Federative Socialist
Советская Федеративная Социалистическая
Republic
Республика
what was you said that Russia appeared in
что было ты сказал что Россия появилась
94 before that in 92 93 not  it was to
94 году до что в 92 93 не было чтобы
look, take
посмотри возьми
93, the constitution of the Russian appeared
93 году появилась конституция Российской
When the life of the
Когда закончилась жизнь
Russian secular Socialist
Российская светская Социалистическая
Republic ended
Республика
when it ceased
когда она перестала
91 years 192 1991 after 91 there
91 год 192 1991 после 91 года никакого
was none
нет не было
By the way, you know an interesting map
Кстати у тебя карта знаешь интересный
look about the RSFSR
посмотри про РСФСР Давай свободных
your existence Now let's say look on
существование свое Сейчас скажем смотри
December 25, 1991, the official
25 декабря 1991 года официальное
name of the state was changed to the
название государства было изменено на
Russian Federation That is, you
Российской Федерации То есть вы
officially call it from the Russian
официально называете с Российской
Federation since December 25, 1991
Федерации с 25 декабря 1991 года
which was in 93,
Конституции которая была в 93 году имел
did Yeltsin have the right to dissolve parliament
ли Ельцин право распустить парламент
and the constitution of the Russian Federation was
а конституция Российской федерации была
adopted in 93 in December, but the
принята в 93 году в декабре вот а та
Constitution that was in 93 did
Конституция которая была в 93 году имел
you have elections throughout the
ли и у вас были выборы во всем
Constitution was yes which was at that
Конституции было да которая была на тот
time 93  Yeltsin when he shot
момент 93 году Ельцин когда расстреливал
the parliament from tanks Find me the way to the
из танков парламент Найди мне путь
Constitution, which said that
Конституции в которой было сказано что
Yeltsin the president has the right to dissolve
Ельцин президент имеет право распустить
the parliament on this I have the
парламент по этой у меня у меня к тебе
Russian Federation 91 years old for you
Российской Федерации 91 года было вас
Look at your Constitution, which is new,
Смотри у вас Конституция которая новая
it replaced the old Constitution, you did not
она заменила старую Конституцию вы не
live without the Constitution  You want to say
жили без Конституции Ты хочешь сказать
that you lived without the Constitution, not parliament,
что вы жили без Конституции не парламент
he dissolved parliament if he dissolved
он распустил парламент если распустил
parliament,
парламент
he dissolved and made elections, appointed
он распустил и сделал выборы назначил
new elections
новый выборы
Show me the paragraph of the Constitution according to which
Покажи мне пункт Конституции по которому
Yeltsin had the right to dissolve parliament,
Ельцин имел право распустить парламент
come on Look for the Constitution in the New Year
Ищи в Новом году появилась Конституция
93 watch 93 you had a
93 смотреть 93 году у вас было
Constitution  according to which you lived according to which
Конституция по которой вы жили по
you had elections according to which it
которой у вас были выборы по которой это
was not this what was the Constitution
было не этого какая была Конституция еще
look again don’t care What
раз смотри пофиг Какая у вас была
constitution you had the real Constitution wait
Конституция действительная Конституция
I mean don’t care what
подожди В смысле пофиг Какая
you want to say before 94
ты хочешь сказать до 94 А когда есть
93 years old october
месяц был 93 года октябрь
no october
нет октябрь
well 3 4 october 93 years old Dude I'm already 20
Ну 3 4 октября 93 года Чувак я уже 20
events 3 4
события 3 4
september
сентября
4 october there were military operations
4 октября были боевые действия
Yes, what are you Yes, just before that, he
Да ты что Да так вот сами перед этим он
dissolved the parliament Open the parliament for me
распустил парламент Открой мне
come on Go to Google again
парламента ну-ка Зайди в Google еще раз
no Look
нет Смотри
tell me  to me the paragraph of the Constitution on which
скажи мне пункт Конституции по которым
Yeltsin dissolved parliament Come on,
Ельцин распустил парламент Давай
if you tell me the paragraph of the Constitution on
если ты скажи мне пункт Конституции по
which Yeltsin dissolved the parliament,
которому Ельцин распустил парламент
tell me and I admit that I'm wrong Let's
скажи и я признаю что я не прав Давай
tell me on what paragraph of the Constitution you don't have
скажи по какому пункту Конституции нет у
93 years illegally all of the Russian
вас 93 года незаконно все Российской
Federation because Yeltsin did not make an
Федерации потому что Ельцин сделал не
unconstitutional coup  because
антиконституционный переворот потому что
he did not have the right to dissolve the parliament according to the
он не имел права распускать парламент по
Constitution that was the
той Конституции которая была
Supreme Council could not dissolve
Верховный Совет не мог распускать
President
президент
Yeltsin dissolved the Supreme Council
Ельцин распустил Верховный Совет
dispersed the constitutional court usurped
разогнал конституционный суд узурпировал
power and since then you are an illegal
власть так и с тех пор вы незаконное
political entity
политическое образование
or that Yeltsin shot Wait
или что расстрелял Ельцин Подожди
first you tell me what it all started
сначала ты мне скажи чего все началось
This  later you have a civil war,
Это уже потом у вас гражданская война
we are no longer interested in whom your people will be shot
нам уже не интересно кого там расстрелят
Civil war in the Russian
ваши Гражданская война в Российской
Federation Yes, you citizens of Russia
Федерации Да вы граждане России
shot citizens of Russia You tell me
расстреляли граждан России Ты мне скажи
Yeltsin on the basis of what paragraph of
Ельцин на основании какого пункта
the Constitution dissolved parliament Let me
Конституции распустил парламент Давай я
not let you go until you run away on
тебя не отпущу пока ты не убежишь ни на
any topic  tell me Yeltsin had the right to
какую тему скажи Ельцин имел право
dissolve the parliament or did not have it Tell
распускать парламент или не имел Назови
me the paragraph of the Constitution on which paragraph of the
мне пункт Конституции по какому пункту
Constitution
Конституции
Name the paragraph Where where did you have what was the
Назови пункт Где где у вас что было
presidential parliament No
президентская парламентская Нет
show the
покажи
paragraph of the Constitution and the Supreme Show which
пункт Конституции и Верховного Покажи
Constitution
какой Конституции
Show the paragraph of the Constitution No show where it is
Покажи пункт Конституции Нет покажи где
written that he has the right Show
такое написано что он имеет право Покажи
open  open
открой открой
you sucker open the Constitution Come on
ты [__] откроешь Конституцию Давай давай
Tell me the point on which
Назови мне пункт по которому от какого
year from which year the Constitution
года от какого года Конституция
was before 93 Tell me tell me
до 93 года было Назови мне назови мне
what point according to that current
так какой пункт по той действующей
Constitution
Конституции
from what year to 93
от какого года до 93 года была
the Constitution of the Russian Federation was, look,
Конституция Российской Федерации смотри
I will tell you the Constitution in  In 93, the
я тебе расскажу Конституция в 93 году
Constitution of the USSR was in force as
действующий был Конституция СССР в
amended on December 9, 10, 1992, that
редакции от 9 10 декабря 1992 года то
is, in the ninety-second year So you,
есть В девяносто втором году Так вы
being the Russian Federation, Yes, you accepted
будучи Российской Федерации Да приняли
the renewal of the Constitution and
обновление Конституции так и до 93 года
lived according to this Constitution until 93 before the unconstitutional coup
до неконституционного переворота жили по
Yes, I opened it like this and I
этой Конституции Да вот я открыл так и
look Here is the first  the first chapter, the basis of the
смотрю Вот первый первая глава основа
social system and politics of the
общественного строя и политики
Russian Federation, is the Constitution of
Российской Федерации это Конституция
Changes on
измен
December 10, 92, so the basis of the
10 декабря 92 года так основа
social system and politics of the Russian
общественной строй и политики Российской
Federation, the political system, there is
Федерации политическая система нету
no dissolver, dissolution,
не имеет права роспуска либо
dissolution.
приостановление деятельности съезда
deputies of the Russian Federation The
народных депутатов Российской Федерации
Supreme Council of the Russian Federation
Верховный Совет Российской Федерации
Article 6 1 paragraph 11
Статья 6 1 пункт 11
what is there 109 Come on Come on come on
что там 109 Давай давай
109 no
А ну давай 109 нет
there is nothing here that the president should
статьи нету тут ничего что президент
read by me
моими прочитать
Read
Прочитай
one of them to direct the activities of the world to the
один из направлять деятельность света в
People's Deputies of the Russian Federation,
Народный депутатов Российской Федерации
everyone ran away
все убежал
loshara In short, everyone pancake fried him 30
лошара Короче все блин прожарили его 30
which pancake
который блин
Krasava is we his Sofia Perovskaya
Красава это ж мы его Софии Перовской он
once a week I come across her in the fry
раз в неделю мне попадается её в жарю
This dude wanted us  to tell us
Это чувак нам хотел рассказать у нас там
something illegal there in 93, yes, look, for
что-то незаконно 93 год да смотри
the first time this Clone generally said that the
первый раз этот Клон вообще говорил что
Russian Federation was not in the fourth
Российской Федерации не было четвёртого
year of ninety-four that it was the RSFSR
года девяносто четвёртого что было РСФСР
they dipped it dipped according to the Constitution Yes, you
макнули его макнули по Конституции Да
open it, I specifically found it Yes, because
открываешь я специально нашел Да потому
he was more thinking like suckers  not
что он было более думал типа на лохов не
In short, we as lawyers Yes, we are referring to
Короче мы как юристы Да мы Обращаемся к
documents I opened the Constitution that
документов Я открыл Конституцию которая
was in force Yes as of September
действовала Да на состояние сентябрь
October 93
октябрь 93 года
It was the Constitution Yes, as amended on
Это было Конституция Да с изменениями 9
December 9, 1992, and it clearly says It
декабря 1992 года и там четко сказано
clearly says So,
Вот четко сказано Так Так
the President of the Russian Federation does not
вот президент Российской Федерации не
have the right to dissolve either
имеет права роспуска либо
suspension of the activities of the Congress of
приостановление деятельности съезда
People's Deputies of the Russian Federation of the
народных депутатов Российской Федерации
Supreme Council of the Russian Federation, that
Верховного Света Российской Федерации то
is, Yeltsin, in 93, in violation of the
есть Ельцин в 93 году нарушении
Constitution, the
Конституции
current one dissolved the Supreme Council, of
действующий распустил Верховный Совет
course, the supreme light, the Constitution
естественно верховный свет в Конституции
directly says not only that there is
прямо сказано не то что там
uncertainty, it directly says that
неопределенность там прямо сказано что
the president has no right to dissolve the
президент не имеет права распускать
Parliament of the Supreme Council of the Russian
парламент Верховный Совет Российской
Federation
Федерации
and  appealed immediately to the Constitutional Court
и обратились сразу в Конституционный суд
Yeltsin, yes, usurped power, dispersed the
Ельцин да узурпировал власть разогнал
constitutional court and shot from
конституционный суд и расстрелял из из
tanks to the parliament and the defenders of
танков до парламент и защитников
the parliament who came out to defend
парламента которые вышли на защиту
democracy. Therefore, since 93, the Russian
демократии Поэтому с 93 года Российской
Federation does not exist as a state
Федерации не существует как государство
because Yeltsin seized power, spent
потому что Ельцин захватил власть провел
further already changed the Constitution in 93
дальше уже изменил Конституцию в 93 году
right there 94 after that
сразу там 94 после этого Вот и
So the peoples have the right to
народы так имеют право на
self-determination because for 93 years we
самоопределение потому что 93 года мы
have under the name of the Russian Federation
имеем под названием Российской Федерации
it does not exist she died in 93
её не существует она умерла в 93 году
after Yeltsin violated the Constitution and
после нарушения ельцином Конституции и
shot down the parliament Yeltsin and his
расстрелом парламента Ельцин и его
oligarchs usurped power then
олигархи узурпировали власть потом
transferred this power to Putin yes  When
передали эту власть Путину да Когда
Yeltsin, in an illegal way, also on
Ельцин внезаконный способ также в
New Year's Eve, the
новогоднюю ночь попла сказал я передаю
[ __ ] said, in short, here's the successor, and now the power
короче вот преемнику да теперь власть
Here and still This is the
Вот и до сих пор Вот это
clique that seized power in 93
клика которая захватила власть в 93 году
in the Russian Federation illegally this is the
в Российской Федерации незаконно вот это
junta she is in power and she kills
хунта она при власти и она убивает
peoples robs peoples and abandons  them to go to
народы грабит народы и бросает их на
war in other countries Therefore, the
войны в другие страны Поэтому
sacred mission of every citizen of the
священная миссия каждого гражданина
Russian Federation Yes, to
Российской Федерации Да
fight this junta that has settled in
бороться с этой хунтай которая засела в
the Kremlin, which, since the age of 93, in violation of
Кремле которая с 93 года в нарушении
the Constitution, has shot the
Конституции расстреляла из танков
parliament of its parliament from tanks, that is, the children of
парламент свой парламент то есть детей
women, adults, everyone who was there crushed
женщин взрослых все кто там был давили
people with tanks, it was terrible  a terrible
танками людей это было ужасное ужасное
sight so all people go over
зрелище поэтому все люди до переходите
to the side of the rebels Yes there are Russian
на сторону повстанцев Да есть российские
volunteer corps if it is Russia yes
добровольческие корпус если он России да
come find contacts go to
приходите находите контакты выезжаете в
other countries find
другие страны находите
recruiting centers join
рекрутинговые центры присоединяйтесь
because the Belgorod region has already
потому что Белгородская область уже
begun the restoration of the constitutional
начала восстановление конституционного
order on the territory of the Russian Federation
строя на территории Российской Федерации
Bryansk region also tried now
Брянская область тоже пробовала сейчас
Kursk is joining  vronizhnaya but the whole
подключается Курская вронижная но вся
Russian Federation should blaze
Российская Федерация должна полыхать Да
Yes, these high fur boots that have settled in the Kremlin
вот эти унты которые засела в Кремле
their henchmen in the regions they
ихний приспешники в регионах у них
should burn the Earth under their feet
должно гореть Земля под ногами потому
because only through the freedom of peoples can you
что только через свободу народов можно
get the freedom of man all countries
получить свободу человека все страны
free Yakutia free Buryatia
свободные Якутия свободная Бурятия
free peoples of the Caucasus Freedom peoples of the
свободные народы Кавказа Свободы народы
Urals of the Volga region India  must become
Урала Поволжья Индия должны стать
free Peter must finally
свободной Питер должен стать наконец-то
get rid of the yoke of Moscow and become an
избавиться от московского ига и стать
independent European prosperous
независимым европейским процветающим
city every Russian is enough to sit
городом каждый россиянин Хватит сидеть
idly by the Russian junta and these
сложа руки российской хунта и вот эти
propagandists who are on the payroll of
пропагандоны которые сидят на зарплате у
the Kremlin they want you to give your
Кремля они хотят чтобы ты отдавал свои
money to Moscow and die for Moscow
деньги в Москву и умирал за Москву
gave money to Moscow died for Moscow
отдавал деньги в Москву умирал за Москву
this is their understanding of your life but you
это есть их понимании твоя жизнь но ты
can change Join the rebels
можешь изменить Вступай повстанцам